Why are you drinking tea alone?
Where is your sister-in-law?
She
went out to play golf early in the morning.
Oh.
Hey.
What's wrong
with your face?
Ah.
It's nothing.
I bumped into something.
Oh,
how can you get a five-finger print?
Ah,
it seems that
the fiancée of the Lu family
is a thorny wild rose.
You investigated me?
Oh,
I dare not.
Zhuang Wan told me.
Oh,
I never thought
I'd see you
lose your mind
over a woman in your lifetime.
Grandpa,
I'll leave if you keep this up.
Hey,
it's just a slap.
What's the big deal?
I was even slapped three times
when I was pursuing your grandma.
I like Jiang Li
very much.
She's a bit like your grandma.
Grandpa,
how did you
pursue my grandma?
I...
Three words.
Never give up.
and
sincerity.
Isn't that just pestering?
If you really want to be with her,
don't try to remove her thorn,
but learn to tolerate the pain it causes.
After a long time,
it becomes an addiction in your bones.
What if her thorn
is poisonous?
Then learn to be her antidote.
But
I have to remind you that
if you really love her,
you should get her out of the quagmire
of the Lu family as soon as possible.
I don't allow Zhuang Wan
to invest in the Lu family
with the capital of the Shen family
for a certain reason.
What's the reason?
Because Annie is a cobra.
Once bitten by it,
there's no cure.
Oh,
it seems the young master
is more obedient than I thought.
You'd better know some secrets.
Your deal with Jiang Li
and your love for Lu Qianqian
are enough to make me...
Did Li Xiaorou tell you?
Can't I find this out myself?
Li Xiaorou, you bitch!
Unless you've planted a bug on me!
Come on.
Take a swing.
Not interested.
Negotiation is like the first shot in golf.
It's not about the perfect landing,
but about finding the other side's bottom line,
so you know your next move.
Tell me.
What do you want?
Shouldn't you ask
what I can offer you?
Then tell me.
What can you offer me?
To help you get Lu Qianqian.
Nice.
Just like the love
hidden in your heart.
The force is strong enough.
Unfortunately,
you didn't guess the wind direction.
Tell me.
How can you help me?
You haven't answered me.
Do you want the golden throne
or
the girl
you love?
Is there a contradiction?
I'm the successor of the Golden Thread.
You seem to be
Annie's puppet.
You need her approval to hate,
let alone love.
I'm telling you,
Lu Qianqian is Zhou Jian's woman.
Zhou Jian will be kicked out of the Lu family.
And then?
Let Jiang Li take over the company?
She's a woman who's
full of ambition.
She's just a tissue to me.
I'll throw her away after using her.
It doesn't matter
what ambition she has.
Then there's nothing to talk about.
Well,
as a viewer,
I can enjoy such a wonderful show.
It's not a loss.
Tell me more.
I might be interested.
I'll use 5% of Lingshan Electric's
shares under Shen Family's name
as collateral
to get your signature on the agreement.
And you'll still own 15% of
Golden Thread's shares.
I just want a say in Golden Thread.
You don't seem like someone who likes losing money.
When trapped animals lick each other's wounds,
who cares if the cage is gilded or not?
Besides,
it's worth to get a foothold
outside the Shen Family.
Dark Fairy Tale Grand Show Countdown seven days.
You're as calm as a dead pond.
I'm just the one who hands over the knife,
but you're the one who holds it.
You're so calm that it's scary.
Tell me,
what have you been through?
For example, you collude with brother-in-law
to eat away at the Lu family's empire.
You'd better behave yourself.
I feel that Lu Qianqian has been acting strange lately.
Ah.
I also feel so.
After the wedding,
she has been treating me coldly.
I guess you haven't been spending enough time with her lately.
Only when a woman puts on a wedding dress,
when she wears the wedding dress,
she gives her heart to you.
Spend more time with her.
She has 15% of the shares,
which is the final bonus of Dark Fairy Tale.
You always say
The show's success is the first step.
What are you planning?
When Pandora's box is opened,
disaster and surprise are always twins.
By the way,
Lu Xu has begun to suspect me recently.
If he knows you betrayed him,
he can do anything.
If he hurts me,
will you protect me?
No need to answer.
I believe you.
Let's play another round.
Hello, the number you dialed is invalid.
Please check and redial.
[Hello,]
[the number you've dialed is not answered.]
Bitch.
Aren't you on vacation?
A long vacation
is just a fancy way of saying you're fired.
Young Master,
just wait for me.
I'll get you back.
Are you waiting
for Jiang Li to finish the divorce plan
or wait for her to get rid of
Zhou Jian, the stumbling block?
Who told you that?
Oh, young master,
she's not here to help you.
She's the ghost of Su Muchen seeking revenge.
Look,
what she wants to destroy
is the entire Lu family.
Tell me your conditions.
Well,
bring down Jiang Li,
and let me back to the designer position.
Aren't you the Old Madam's man?
Why are you coming to me instead of her?
I really didn't get it wrong.
You're really very sharp.
Because I found out some secrets
that I shouldn't have found out.
To protect myself,
I have to come to you.
So,
I hope that after everything is done,
I can become
your subordinate.
You finally came home today.
You killed the Lu family with my hand.
How dare you, Jiang Li!
What are you laughing at?
Are you afraid
Afraid Annie will know you let the wolf in?
I really underestimated you.
How did you know
what happened over 20 years ago?
You Lus are
just like scorpions in the desert,
only stinging people in the shadows.
Do you think you can
shake the Lu family?
Do you know the bell toad?
The weakest creature
can kill all the fish in a pond.
With Annie as your backing,
you bully those weak people
in the outside world.
You hide and shiver in danger.
Do you think Mumu will be more like Zhou Jian
or you?
You...
Who are you?
I am a lone wolf in the desert.
But you are not a hunter.
But it doesn't matter.
When you do what I want,
you will also get
what you want.
Now,
the rules of the game
are up to me.
Ah.
What's wrong with your face?
Lu Xu wants to rape Sister Qianqian.
Brother-in-law, stop him.
Liu Yanyan,
take Jiang Li to stop the bleeding.
Aunt Xu, call the police.
Okay.
He knows our secret.
You bitch.
You tricked me.
Zhou Jian.
Stop, Zhou Jian.
We've all been tricked.
Lu Xu.
Zhou Jian.
Let me explain.
We've all been tricked.